

CONTACT

Location

: seksyen 13, Shah alam

Email

: xxganesh84@gmail.com

Phone Number

: 0124964556

LANGUAGE

English:

spoken -written -

Bahasa Malaysia:

• spoken -

Tamil:
• spoken -

• written -

GANESH KUMAR A/L SUNDRAM

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I have recently completed my internship , with experience in Designing UI , apps manual testing and troubleshooting PC. I am also open to learning new technology and skills to improvise myself.

Self Learning - Front end development(HTML, CSS and JavaScript)

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Computer Engineering (Hons)
Management & Science University | 2019 - 2021
Dean list award on semester 9 (gpa: 3.85 / cgpa: 3.16)

Diploma in Computer Engineering Management & Science University | 2016 - 2019

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM) Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Changlun | 2013

TRAINING

ICT Competencies (IT Programmer)Selangor Human Resource Development Centre (SHRDC) | Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

- UIUX Course using Adobe XD
- Database Management System Course using MYSQL
- Web Application Development Course using Laravel
- Technology Stack Development Course using RESTAPI(Web App) & Xamarin (Mobile App)

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT



HTML



CSS



ADOBE XD



MYSQL



CERTIFICATES

Code Academy-learn HTML Course / Feb 2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT SUPPORT(INTERNSHIP)

GAJA MOVE DELIVERIES SDN BHD | Oct 2021 - April 2022

- Manual app testing for user and riders app.
- The errors/bugs were documented in excel form . This lead to 50% decreased from the errors/ bugs.
- Handling IT related issues such as Improved pc speed, pc setup, upgrading storage.
- Enhancing User app by enhancing the UI design using a software called Figma.

SERVICE CREW

TGV INDULGE | Dec 2016 - Dec 2020

- Answered customer inquiries by phone and responded promptly.
- Trained contracted employees on work and tasks, monitoring work for safety, efficiency and overall project progress.
- Operated POS systems, handling over RM3000 in cash daily.
- Providing satisfactory services to customers for a better experience in cinema and dine-in experience
- Handling monthly inventory stock-take to keeping track of new and expired items and rotating stock

EDUCATIONAL SUPPLY TECHNICIAN

SCIENSCOPE SDN BHD(INTERNSHIP) | Oct 2017 - Jan 2018

- Building and analyses errors in educational supplies such as motor control starter and electrical machine training system.
- Supplied and demonstrate the usage of educational supply at Giatmara Raub, Pahang
- Attained experience in constructing PCB layout by using the software.

VOLUNTERS AND LEADERSHIP

COMPETITIONS

- EXPLORING & BUILD ELECTRONIC CIRCUIT COMPETITION February 2019
- Led a group of 2 people, constructed a circuit that lights up as a blinking heart shape and won 3rd prize.

COMPETITIONS

- Ent Academic Competition: Engineered your Sculpture September 2019
- Guided a group of 3 students to sculpture a plane using copper wire, and we won the 2nd prize in this competition.

COMPETITIONS

- Ent major mentoring: Envi Race February 2021
- In my role as a committee, created a video for the closing ceremony of envirace. Participated by 200+ including students and lecturers

COMMUNITY SERVICE

- Environment (save the turtle (turtle conservation Centre cleaning Pangkor, Perak)) September 2019
- As a team, we cleaned the beach, disposing of plastics, wood, etc. That is caused by human being contamination.